const flashCards = [
  {
    question: "What's the name of this hackathon?",
    answer: "blueprint",
  },
  {
    question: "Where does this hackathon take place?",
    answer: "online",
  },
  {
    question: "Is this hackathon open to middle school students?",
    answer: "no",
  },
  {
    question: "How many web development tracks are there in the learnathon?",
    answer: "two",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Brain of the computer that performs instructions defined by software",
    answer: "CPU",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Set of instructions that tells the hardware what to do. It is what guides the hardware and tells it how to accomplish each task.",
    answer: "Software",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Software used to control the computer and its peripheral equipment.",
    answer: "OS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Groupings of 1's and 0's that makes information that a computer can understand.",
    answer: "Binary",
  },
  {
    question: "translates source code into machine code one line at a time",
    answer: "Interpreter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Storage device that stores digitally encoded data on rapidly rotating rigid disks with magnetic surfaces. The device is either permanently installed within the computer case or can be portable",
    answer: "Hard Drive",
  },
  {
    question:
      "temporary place to store material that works quickly. erased when computer turns off. Volatile.",
    answer: "RAM",
  },
  {
    question: "How many main tracks are there in Blueprint?",
    answer: "four",
  },
];

export default flashCards;
